I think of K-12 teachers in the
我认为公立学校的
public schools as being among our culture heroes.
K-12教师是我们的文化英雄。
In the sense that
在这个意义上，
they're being asked to solve every problem
他们被要求解决这个社会中
that no one else in this society knows how to solve.
没有人知道如何解决的所有问题。
And on a daily basis
他们每天都会
being beat up for their alleged
因为所谓的无能或
inability or inadequacies in doing so.
不足而备被打击。
The best of them are working under
他们中最优秀的人是在
enormously adverse circumstances
极其不利的环境下工作的，
in which there's very little public
在这种环境下，公众对
understanding of what it means to be a teacher
成为一名教师意味着什么
or of how to deal with the
或如何处理教师必须
problems that teachers have to deal with.
处理的问题知之甚少。
And yet they're doing it with great passion,
然而，教师们却以极大的热情，
with great heart, with great commitment.
以极大的诚意，以极大的承诺来进行教学。